Guide to the Gene Feist papers
The New York Public Library. Billy Rose Theatre Division.
- Series II: Roundabout Theatre Company, 1965-2000; 30 boxes
  - Photographs and slides of productions, 1967-1973, undated
    - Photographs
      - Man and Superman, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - A Man for All Seasons, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - The Master Builder, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - The Master Builder, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Master Class, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - The Matchmaker, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - A Member of the Wedding, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - The Miracle Worker, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Misalliance, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Misalliance, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - The Miser, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - The Miser, 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Miss Julie, 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Miss Julie, 1982-1983 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Mistress of the Inn, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - A Month in the Country, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Mr. Shandy, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Mrs. Warren's Profession, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Naked, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Of Mice and Men, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Old Times, 1983 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - On Approval, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Othello, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Pelleas and Melisande, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Pelleas and Melisande, 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - The Philanderer, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - The Philanderer, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Pins and Needles, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Pins and Needles, 1978 (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Pirates on Parade, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - The Play's the Thing, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - The Playboy of the Western World, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Playing with Fire, 1982-1983 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Price of Fame, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - The Promise, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Pygmalion, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - A Raisin in the Sun, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Rashomon, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - The Rehearsal, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - The Rehearsal, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Right You Are If You Think You Are, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - The Rivals, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - The Rivals, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Room Service, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - Rosencranz and Guildenstern Are Dead, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Rosmersholm, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Rosmersholm, 1974 (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - The Seagull, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - The Seagull, 1973 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - She Stoops to Conquer, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - She Stoops to Conquer, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - She Stoops to Conquer, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - She Stoops to Conquer, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 28)
      - The Show-Off, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Springtime for Henry, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Streetsongs, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 21)
      - The Subject was Roses, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 22)
      - Summer and Smoke, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 23)
      - Summer and Smoke, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 29)
      - The Taming of the Shrew, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 24)
      - A Taste of Honey, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - The Tempest, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Trumpets and Drums, 1984-1985 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Uncle Vanya, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Uncle Vanya, 1971 (Box 68, Folder 30)
      - The Voice of the Turtle, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Waiting for Lefty, 1967-1968 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Waiting for Lefty, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 31)
      - Waltz of the Toreadors, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - The Wax Museum, 1971-1972 (Box 68, Folder 32)
      - What Every Woman Knows, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - What Every Woman Knows, 1974-1975 (Box 68, Folder 33)
      - Winners, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - The Winslow Boy, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - The World of Shalom Aleichem, 1976 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - The World of Shalom Aleichem, 1976 (Box 68, Folder 34)
      - Yolanda Loves Me, 1966-1967 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - You Never Can Tell, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 13)
      - Unknown Productions, undated (Box 72, Folder 14)
      - Various Photographs, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
      - Various Photographs, undated (Box 68, Folder 35)
      - Slides, Multiple Productions, 1960s-1980s (Box 72, Folder 16-17)
      - Unsorted (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 48, Folder 6-7)
  - Posters and drawings, Undated (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Posters and drawings (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Posters and drawings, 1968-1995 (Box 70, Folder 2-3)
  - Production files, 1978-1998
    - Cabaret (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Candida (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - The Country Girl (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Dance of Death (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Dance Umbrella (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - A Day in the Death of Joe Egg (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Fanny's First Play (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - The Father (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Ghosts (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
    - Missed Opportunities (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Of Mice and Men (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Rashomon (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - The Rover (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - The Seagull (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Selling Off (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - She Stoops to Conquer (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
    - She Stoops to Conquer (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Tramway Road (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - Twelfth Night (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Various (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
  - Production scrapbooks, 1966-1990
    - Alphabetical
      - Ah, Wilderness-Dance of Death (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - The Dark at the Top of the Stairs-Ghosts (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Hamlet-The Knack (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - The Lady from Maxim's-Misalliance (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - The Miser-The Rivals (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Room Service-You Never Can Tell (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Chronological
      - 1966 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 1966-1995
    - Alphabetical
      Photocopies of programs
      - Ah, Wilderness-Jeeves Takes Charge (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - John Gabriel Borkmanx-Rosmersholm (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - The Seagull-Yolanda Loves Me (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Chronological
      - Early programs (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - 1966-1972 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - 1973-1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - 1977-1979 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - 1980 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - 1984-1985 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - 1985-1987 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - 1989-1990 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - 1991-1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Unsorted (Box 57, Folder 3-4)
  - Publicity materials, 1986-2000 (Box 58, Folder 1-3)
  - Set designs, 1981-1989
    Photographs and drawings
    - 17th St. (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 23rd St. (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - 26th St. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Submitted plays, 1988-1990
    - Mrs. Klein (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Their Finest Hour--Churchill and Murrow, In My Father's House (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - The White Devil (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Theatres, 1965-1995
    - 17th St. (Box 59, Folder 1-10)
    - 23rd St. (Halou Cinema) (Box 60, Folder 1-10)
    - 26th St. (Susan Bloch American Jewish Theatre) (Box 61, Folder 1-11)
    - 28th St. (Church of the Holy Apostle) (Box 61, Folder 12-13)
    - Lucille Lortel Theatre (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Theatre rentals (Box 61, Folder 15)